[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Hey, something just occurred to me.
Why do microbiologists
need a missile silo?
That would be like our department
having a... medical bay.
Mm, my gun feels light; I should reload.
I suppose it's possible I won't encounter
anyone else hostile tonight, but...
no, that's not possible.
Yeah, it even has the red glow
of Hell lighting there.
There must be a way out of here
that doesn't go straight through Hell.
Well, if there's one thing I've
learned today,
it's that missile launches are
not like the movies at all.
I thought there were all these procedures,
two different people with special keys,
a small crew of people to
monitor all the systems,
but no. It's just a big red
button that says "Launch".
[gunshot]
DAAAH!
WHERE THE FUCK DID THAT COME FROM?!
[gunshot]
YEEE!
I GOT IT THE FIRST TIME!
I didn't see anyone.
I may have seen a muzzle flash...
I don't know...
Blehblblbluh...
Okay...
Blehblehbleh...?
Maybe I've been too hasty to judge
about that underground passage.
It's starting to look better now.
Okay, go go go go go!
Mehnuhn?
Mehnununbid...?
Then we're all in agreement,
let's take the ladder.
Yeah, better to reign in Hell
than... get shot on the surface.
Christ, those rounds left a
pockmark on this suit.
I'm going to have welt marks for sure.
Ah, another tram.
I'm going to be depressed if all
this does is loop back to the old track.
The hell is this?
It looks like some sort of camera...?
Can I sell this?
It looks like good quality,
whatever it is.
Does this come out?
No.
Oh, wait, there's some sort of
trigger on the back.
[powering up]
[chirps]
Oh. Oh!
I saw these.
Okay, I think I'm done messing
with this one.
I don't want to touch it anymore.
I'll take this one.
I just hope it doesn't turn on
while I'm carrying it.
What the hell... it's like I'm
caught fishing line... there we go.
All right, um... on.
Hm, I just thought of a paradox.
Maybe the more people I kill,
the less likely I am to be the fall guy.
Because, sure, they could say I
killed five or ten people,
but can they really pin dozens and
dozens of armed military personnel on me?
[tram squealing]
I think--WHAT?  NO! NO NO NO!
NOT AGAIN! I'M OUT!
Ah ah! Uniform! Unif--
New Yorkers talk like
they're all big and bad,
I bet they don't deal with half
of this shit in the subway.
I think if I ever hear someone
complain about their commute again,
I'm just going to punch them in the face.
"My drive home's worse than yours."
Well, that's two more to add to the count.
Yeah, I think it's going to hard sell
pinning all these killings on just me.
What's this?
This is useless. This doesn't go anywhere.
What?
Anyway, my background
doesn't fit the profile:
no military training,
never fired a gun,
acquitted for petty theft,
not a member of any
extremist organizations,
has PhD in a theoretical physics.
Yeah, that sounds like our man.
What the hell is this room?
I guess this is an
abandoned missile silo,
since we got enough funding to
just keep making more of them.
Of course, no ladder, no stairs.
Guess I'll just drop down.
So, who are some other spree killers?
There's Timothy McVeigh.
He had military training.
Well, Lee Harvey Oswald
wasn't a spree killer,
but he received about as much government
attention as I'm getting right now.
He had military training...
and was an extremist.
Ugh, that's gross.
Hey! Get a room, you two!
This is a FAMILY missile silo.
I have nothing more to say to you.
Who else?
Charles Whitman, military training.
I'm a hard sell.
I think--
Christ, you people were
under the stairway.
This place is low class.
Let's see.
Alvin York killed dozens of
people and he was a hero.
He didn't even want to; he was like me.
Am I a hero?
Eh, I don't know.
I don't think it's heroic if the only
person you're saving is yourself.
I'll take that.
Dammit, this whole place is flooded.
Well, I'm running out of options here.
All roads lead to water.
It would help if I had a clue
where I was going.
I can't see a damned thing.
Eh, screw it, maybe I'll find
somebody's car keys.
[underwater mumbling]
[underwater panicking]
[gasping]
WHAT GIVES?!
SOMETHING WAS BITING ME DOWN THERE!
This pool sucks, I'm getting out!
At least, I think I am.
I'm having that sinister feeling again
where every hallway here looks it loops
back in on itself for no damned reason.
Steady...
Shit!
[underwater mumbling]
Yeah, the water is always
wetter on the other side.
What the--
What the hell is that?
It looks like a prison guard tower.
I don't get it.
This place makes no sense.
[underwater mumbling]
...it's unconstitutional...
Okay, that passage is the
only one left, I think.
I'll check out.
If it I looks good, I'll keep going.
If it doesn't, I'll come back...
or die, I guess.
No.
[underwater panicking]
[underwater straining]
[gagging]
[gasping]
Oh dear God...
Oh God...
Oh jeez...
Oh... oh...
Okay, I think I'll take a breather.
Oh man. That sucked.
And those worms or
whatever keep BITING ME!
BLAGH!